[{"entities": [["2010", "DATE"], ["Insurance Information Institute", "ORG"], ["978", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 15}, {"entities": [["Insurance Information Institute", "ORG"], ["110", "CARDINAL"], ["StreetNew York", "GPE"], ["NY 10038Tel", "ORG"], ["212", "CARDINAL"], ["212", "CARDINAL"], ["Robert\n\t\nP.\n\t\nHartwig", "PERSON"], ["Ph.D.", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Cary\n\t\nSchneider\n\t\n", "PERSON"], ["Jeanne\n\t\nSalvatore\n\t\n", "PERSON"], ["Steven\n\t\nN.\n\t\nWeisbart", "PERSON"], ["Ph.D.,\n\t\nCLU\n\t\n–\n\t\n", "WORK_OF_ART"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["CLU\n\t\n", "ORG"], ["Claire\n\t\nWilkinson\n\t\n", "PERSON"], ["Neil", "PERSON"], ["Mary-Anne\n\t\nFirneno\n\t\n", "PERSON"], ["Shorna\n\t\nLewis\n\t\n", "ORG"], ["Katja\n\t\nCharlene\n\t\nLewis\n\t\n", "PERSON"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Charlene\n\t\nLewis\n\t\n", "ORG"], ["Ruth\n\t\nGastel", "PERSON"], ["Media\n New", "ORG"], ["Media Relations", "ORG"], ["Michael\n\t\n", "PERSON"], ["Barry\n\t\n", "PERSON"], ["Editorial Services\n\t\n", "ORG"], ["Basora\n\t\n", "PERSON"], ["Loretta\n\t\nWorters\n\t\n", "PERSON"], ["Justin\n\t\nShaddix\n\t\n", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Justin\n\t\nShaddix\n\t\n–\n\t\n", "ORG"], ["California", "GPE"], ["Miller\n\t\n", "ORG"], ["Tel", "PERSON"], ["213", "CARDINAL"], ["213", "CARDINAL"], ["California", "GPE"], ["Lehman\n\t\n–\n\t\n", "ORG"], ["Tel", "PERSON"], ["925-300-9570", "CARDINAL"], ["925-906-9321", "CARDINAL"], ["Davis Communications", "PERSON"], ["William\n\t\nJ.\n\t\nDavis", "PERSON"], ["Atlanta\n\t\n", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["William\n\t\nJ.\n\t\nDavis", "PERSON"], ["Atlanta\n\t\n", "ORG"], ["Tel", "PERSON"], ["770-321-5150", "PRODUCT"], ["770-321-5150", "PRODUCT"], ["Hispanic", "NORP"], ["Elianne\n\t\nGonzález", "PERSON"], ["Miami\n\t\n–\n\t\n", "ORG"], ["Tel", "PERSON"], ["954", "CARDINAL"], ["Florida", "GPE"], ["Lynne\n\t\nMcChristian", "PERSON"], ["Tampa\n\t\n–\n\t\n", "ORG"], ["Tel", "PERSON"], ["813-480-6446", "PRODUCT"], ["813-915-3463", "PRODUCT"], ["2010", "DATE"], ["978", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["over 50 years", "DATE"], ["the Insurance Information Institute", "ORG"], ["I.I.I.", "ORG"], ["I.I.I.", "ORG"]], "topic": 15}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.", "ORG"], ["the years", "DATE"], ["Today", "DATE"], ["I.I.I.", "ORG"]], "topic": 15}, {"entities": [["500", "CARDINAL"], ["over 100", "CARDINAL"], ["LOMA", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Handbook", "PERSON"], ["Institute", "ORG"], ["the Insurance Fact Book", "LAW"], ["the Financial Services Fact Book and A Firm Foundation: How Insurance Supports the Economy", "ORG"], ["•\n Regulators\n•", "ORG"]], "topic": 15}, {"entities": [["•\n Regulators\n•\n Students", "ORG"], ["•\n Academics\nW", "ORG"], ["Handbook", "PERSON"], ["I.I.I.", "ORG"], ["Robert Hartwig", "PERSON"], ["Ph.D., CPCUPresidentInsurance Information Institute\nContents\nInsurance Basics", "ORG"], ["1", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 15}, {"entities": [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["Business Insurance", "ORG"], ["16", "CARDINAL"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["Long-Term Care Insurance", "ORG"], ["22", "CARDINAL"], ["Disability Insurance", "ORG"], ["24", "CARDINAL"], ["27", "CARDINAL"], ["Captives and Other Risk-Financing Options", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["29", "CARDINAL"], ["32", "CARDINAL"], ["Cellphones and Driving", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["34", "CARDINAL"], ["35", "CARDINAL"], ["Credit Scoring", "ORG"], ["39", "CARDINAL"], ["43", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["45", "CARDINAL"], ["Flood Insurance", "ORG"], ["50", "CARDINAL"], ["The Liability System", "ORG"], ["Medical Malpractice \nInsurance", "ORG"], ["52", "CARDINAL"], ["No-Fault Auto Insurance", "ORG"], ["55", "CARDINAL"], ["60", "CARDINAL"], ["62", "CARDINAL"], ["Terrorism Risk and Insurance 69", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["73", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["128", "CARDINAL"], ["Property/Casualty Insurance Industry Organizations", "ORG"], ["128", "CARDINAL"], ["Life/Health Insurance Industry Organizations", "ORG"], ["132", "CARDINAL"], ["Financial Services Industry Organizations", "ORG"], ["134", "CARDINAL"], ["Brokers 141\nRegulatory/Legislative Organizations", "LAW"], ["142", "CARDINAL"], ["143", "CARDINAL"], ["145", "CARDINAL"], ["Actuarial/Accounting", "ORG"], ["145", "CARDINAL"], ["146", "CARDINAL"], ["147", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["147", "CARDINAL"], ["147", "CARDINAL"], ["147", "CARDINAL"], ["Crime/Fraud 147", "ORG"], ["152", "CARDINAL"], ["Ground Transportation 152\nMedical Malpractice/Professional Liability", "ORG"], ["153", "CARDINAL"], ["154", "CARDINAL"], ["154", "CARDINAL"], ["154", "CARDINAL"], ["Safety/Disaster Mitigation", "ORG"], ["155", "CARDINAL"], ["157", "CARDINAL"], ["Title Insurance", "ORG"], ["158", "CARDINAL"], ["158", "CARDINAL"], ["158", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["158", "CARDINAL"], ["158", "CARDINAL"], ["159", "CARDINAL"], ["Associations", "ORG"], ["162", "CARDINAL"], ["190I.I.I.", "CARDINAL"], ["193", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.", "ORG"], ["195I.I.I.", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["1", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["three", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["L/H", "ORG"], ["Medicare", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["The National Association of Insurance Commissioners", "ORG"], ["The McCarran-Ferguson Act", "ORG"], ["Congress", "ORG"], ["1945", "DATE"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["Congress", "ORG"], ["1945", "DATE"], ["1999", "DATE"], ["Gramm-Leach-Bliley Financial Services Modernization Act", "LAW"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["SAP", "ORG"], ["annual", "DATE"], ["the Internal Revenue Service", "ORG"], ["SAP", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Financial Accounting Standards Board", "ORG"], ["FASB", "ORG"], ["The Securities and Exchange Commission", "ORG"], ["SEC", "ORG"], ["the United States", "GPE"], ["SAP", "ORG"], ["2001", "DATE"], ["the International Accounting Standards Board", "ORG"], ["IASB", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["International Financial Reporting Standards", "ORG"], ["2001", "DATE"], ["100", "CARDINAL"], ["IFRS", "ORG"], ["2007", "DATE"], ["SEC", "ORG"], ["U.S.", "GPE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["U.S.", "GPE"], ["2008", "DATE"], ["the National Association of Insurance Commissioners", "ORG"], ["2008", "DATE"], ["FASB", "ORG"], ["IASB", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["the 1990s", "DATE"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["the 1980s", "DATE"], ["Insurance Basics", "PERSON"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Overview\n\t ", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["six months to a year", "DATE"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["six months to a year", "DATE"], ["six", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Medical Payments or Personal Injury Protection", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["3", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["3", "CARDINAL"], ["InsuranceInsurance Basics", "PERSON"], ["4", "CARDINAL"], ["4", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["250", "MONEY"], ["1,000", "MONEY"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["5", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["$100 to $300", "MONEY"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["6", "CARDINAL"], ["Insurance Basics\nAuto Insurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["Auto Insurance\n\t ", "ORG"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["the National Flood Insurance Program", "ORG"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["four", "CARDINAL"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["the Structure of the Home", "WORK_OF_ART"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["about 10 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["2", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["50 to 70 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["about $500", "MONEY"], ["InsuranceInsurance Basics", "PERSON"], ["6", "CARDINAL"], ["3", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["about $100,000", "MONEY"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["about $100,000", "MONEY"], ["at least $300,000", "MONEY"], ["between $200 to $350", "MONEY"], ["1", "MONEY"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["4", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["about 20 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["ten", "CARDINAL"], ["Types of Homeowners Insurance Policies", "ORG"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["Insurance Basics\nHomeowners Insurance\n\t ", "ORG"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["16", "CARDINAL"], ["HO-2", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["16", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["• H0-6", "PERSON"], ["Condo/Co-opA", "ORG"], ["16", "CARDINAL"], ["16", "CARDINAL"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["10", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Riot", "PERSON"], ["commotion• Damage", "ORG"], ["InsuranceInsurance Basics", "PERSON"], ["8", "CARDINAL"], ["Theft• Volcanic", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Standard Homeowners Policy Exclusions\nStandard", "ORG"], ["1", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["the National Flood Insurance Program", "ORG"], ["888", "CARDINAL"], ["250,000", "MONEY"], ["100,000", "MONEY"], ["NFIP", "ORG"], ["47", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["47", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["Tsunamis", "ORG"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["EarthquakesEarthquake", "ORG"], ["Insurance Basics\nHomeowners Insurance\n\t ", "ORG"], ["the California Earthquake Authority", "ORG"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["California", "GPE"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["Damage Resulting", "PERSON"], ["Faulty, Defective or Inadequate” Maintenance,", "WORK_OF_ART"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["MaterialsDefective", "ORG"], ["three", "CARDINAL"], ["1", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["Guaranteed/Extended Replacement Cost", "ORG"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["3", "CARDINAL"], ["Guaranteed/Extended Replacement Cost\nAn", "ORG"], ["20-25 percent", "PERCENT"], ["100,000", "MONEY"], ["20,000", "MONEY"], ["25,000", "MONEY"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["Ordinance or Law", "WORK_OF_ART"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["Ordinance or Law", "WORK_OF_ART"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["InsuranceInsurance Basics", "PERSON"], ["10", "CARDINAL"], ["four", "CARDINAL"], ["1", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Business Interruption Insurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 21}, {"entities": [], "topic": 21}, {"entities": [["three", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["•\t Business\tIncome\tCoverage:\t ", "ORG"], ["Compensates", "NORP"]], "topic": 21}, {"entities": [], "topic": 21}, {"entities": [], "topic": 21}, {"entities": [["Insurance Basics\nBusiness Insurance\n\t ", "ORG"], ["11Protection", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["fed", "ORG"], ["National Flood Insurance Program", "ORG"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["the Terrorism Risk Insurance Act of", "LAW"], ["2002", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Liability Insurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["four", "CARDINAL"], ["• Property damage• Personal", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["12", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["2010", "DATE"], ["1999", "DATE"], ["1999", "DATE"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["2010", "DATE"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["Commercial Vehicle Insurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["3", "CARDINAL"], ["Commercial Vehicle Insurance", "ORG"], ["third", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["4", "CARDINAL"], ["Workers Compensation Insurance", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["Business Insurance\n\t ", "ORG"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Types of Business Coverages", "ORG"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["four", "CARDINAL"], ["fifth", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["1", "CARDINAL"], ["Omissions Insurance/Professional Liability", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Employment Practices Liability Insurance\nEmployment", "ORG"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["Officers Liability Insurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["3", "CARDINAL"], ["Officers Liability Insurance\nDirectors", "ORG"], ["the Business InsuranceInsurance Basics", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["14", "CARDINAL"], ["4", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["Key Person Life Insurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["the Business-Insurance Basics\nBusiness Insurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["Business Insurance\n\t ", "ORG"], ["BOP", "ORG"], ["BOP", "ORG"]], "topic": 21}, {"entities": [["100", "CARDINAL"], ["BOP", "ORG"]], "topic": 21}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["3", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["3", "CARDINAL"], ["Homeowners", "PERSON"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["BOP", "ORG"]], "topic": 21}, {"entities": [["BOP", "ORG"], ["BOP", "ORG"], ["BOP", "ORG"], ["BOP", "ORG"]], "topic": 21}, {"entities": [], "topic": 15}, {"entities": [["16", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tLife Insurance Basics", "ORG"], ["1", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["4", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["January 1, 2011", "DATE"], ["5", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["6", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["6", "CARDINAL"], ["Basics\nLife Insurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Life Insurance\n\t ", "ORG"], ["17Types", "CARDINAL"], ["Life Insurance", "ORG"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["Term Life", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["one to 30 years", "DATE"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["one-year", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["one-year", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Whole Life/Permanent Life\nWhole", "ORG"], ["three", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["1,000", "MONEY"], ["80", "CARDINAL"], ["the early years", "DATE"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["the 1970s", "DATE"], ["1980s", "DATE"], ["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["InsuranceInsurance Basics", "PERSON"], ["18", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Insurance Basics\nLife Insurance\n\t ", "ORG"], ["19Annuities", "CARDINAL"], ["Basics\nAnnuities", "EVENT"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["•\t Primary", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["•\t Premium", "WORK_OF_ART"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["1", "CARDINAL"], ["Tax Deferral on Investment", "ORG"], ["taxed year", "DATE"], ["year", "DATE"], ["401(k)s", "CARDINAL"], ["401(k)s", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["Variety of Investment Options", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Certificate of Deposit", "ORG"], ["recent years", "DATE"], ["AnnuitiesInsurance Basics", "PERSON"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["20", "CARDINAL"], ["4", "CARDINAL"], ["Taxfree Transfers Among Investment Options", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["three", "CARDINAL"], ["6", "CARDINAL"], ["Heirs", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["10 or 20 years", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["10 or 20 years", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"], ["Insurance Basics\nAnnuities\n\t ", "PERSON"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t21annuities", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["December 2008", "DATE"], ["the Securities and Exchange Commission", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["AnnuitiesInsurance Basics", "PERSON"], ["22", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tLong-Term Care Insurance Basics\nLong", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["daily", "DATE"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["daily", "DATE"], ["half", "CARDINAL"], ["the Beginning of Payments\nThe", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["Medical Necessity or Certification", "ORG"], ["Long-Term Care", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["two years", "DATE"], ["Premiums", "PERSON"], ["three to four years", "DATE"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["150", "MONEY"], ["only $130", "MONEY"], ["only $130", "MONEY"], ["20", "MONEY"], ["each day", "DATE"], ["Insurance Basics\nLong-Term Care Insurance\n\t ", "FAC"], ["23some", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["150", "MONEY"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["20 years", "DATE"], ["5 percent", "PERCENT"], ["3 percent", "PERCENT"], ["annual", "DATE"], ["24 years", "DATE"], ["150", "MONEY"], ["daily", "DATE"], ["75", "MONEY"], ["Six", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["Six", "CARDINAL"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["one day", "DATE"], ["seven-day", "DATE"], ["seven days", "DATE"], ["some days", "DATE"], ["some days", "DATE"], ["2", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["4", "CARDINAL"], ["Third-Party Notification", "ORG"], ["5", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["6. Restoration", "CARDINAL"], ["six months", "DATE"], ["Long-Term Care InsuranceInsurance Basics", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["24", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t 24Disability", "ORG"], ["millions", "CARDINAL"], ["Americans", "NORP"], ["each year", "DATE"], ["three", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["three", "CARDINAL"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["Employer-Paid Disability", "ORG"], ["up to 60 percent", "PERCENT"], ["up to five years", "DATE"], ["the age of 65", "DATE"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Social Security Disability", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Social Security Disability", "ORG"], ["at least 12 months", "DATE"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["Individual Disability Income Insurance Policies", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["the Department of Veterans Affairs", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["50 percent to 70 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["Types of Disability Insurance", "ORG"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["0 to 14 days", "DATE"], ["no longer than two years", "DATE"], ["several weeks", "DATE"], ["several months", "DATE"], ["a few years", "DATE"], ["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["every year", "DATE"], ["Insurance Basics\nDisability Insurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["Disability Insurance\n\t ", "ORG"], ["25", "CARDINAL"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["3", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["3", "CARDINAL"], ["COLA", "ORG"], ["COLA", "ORG"], ["4", "CARDINAL"], ["5", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["6", "CARDINAL"], ["90 days", "DATE"], ["Factors Affecting the Choice of a Disability Policy", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["1", "CARDINAL"], ["an initial period of", "DATE"], ["two or three years", "DATE"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["26", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["monthly", "DATE"], ["at least age 65", "DATE"], ["Social Security", "ORG"], ["3", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["3", "CARDINAL"], ["60 percent to 70 percent", "PERCENT"], ["4", "CARDINAL"], ["Either Accidental Injury", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["a decade", "DATE"], ["6", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["6", "CARDINAL"], ["7", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["7", "CARDINAL"], ["8", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["9", "CARDINAL"], ["Financial Stability\nCheck", "ORG"], ["Insurance Basics\nDisablity Insurance\n\t ", "ORG"], ["27", "CARDINAL"], ["Topics", "NORP"], ["28", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 15}, {"entities": [], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["the 1980s", "DATE"], ["the Product Liability Risk Retention Act", "ORG"], ["1981", "DATE"], ["ART", "ORG"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["ART", "ORG"], ["micro-\ninsurance", "PERSON"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["more than one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["the years", "DATE"], ["the United States", "GPE"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["the United States", "GPE"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["30", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"], ["Captives and Other Risk-Financing Options", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Bermuda", "PERSON"], ["20 years ago", "DATE"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["2003", "DATE"], ["the year", "DATE"], ["the Department of Labor", "ORG"], ["Archer Daniels Midland Co.’s", "ORG"], ["Vermont", "GPE"], ["U.S.", "GPE"], ["Vermont", "GPE"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["U.S.", "GPE"], ["Bermuda", "GPE"], ["The Cayman Islands", "GPE"], ["Guernsey", "GPE"], ["British Virgin Islands", "GPE"], ["Luxembourg", "GPE"], ["Barbados", "GPE"], ["Vermont", "GPE"], ["the United States", "GPE"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["II", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["100,000", "MONEY"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["1989", "DATE"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["RRG", "ORG"], ["at least one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["The Risk Retention Act", "LAW"], ["1986", "DATE"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["V. Catastrophe Bonds", "PERSON"], ["Alternative Risk Transfer (", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["ART", "ORG"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["ART", "ORG"], ["One", "CARDINAL"], ["Andrew", "PERSON"], ["Iniki", "ORG"], ["1992", "DATE"], ["Northridge", "ORG"], ["1994", "DATE"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["Zurich Financial’s Kamp Re", "ORG"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["$190 million", "MONEY"], ["2005", "DATE"], ["Hurricane Katrina", "EVENT"], ["multibillion dollar", "MONEY"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["32", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["$25 million", "MONEY"], ["Katrina", "EVENT"]], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [["Hurricane Rita", "EVENT"], ["Category 5", "LAW"], ["the United States", "GPE"], ["the coming years", "DATE"]], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"], ["every decade", "DATE"], ["the Census Bureau", "ORG"], ["USA Today", "ORG"], ["2006", "DATE"], ["34.9 million", "CARDINAL"], ["Atlantic", "LOC"], ["10.2 million", "CARDINAL"], ["1950", "DATE"], ["2005", "DATE"], ["Hurricane Andrew", "EVENT"], ["U.S.", "GPE"]], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [["Andrew", "PERSON"], ["U.S.", "GPE"]], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [["the World Trade Center", "ORG"]], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [["Congress", "ORG"], ["the Terrorism Risk Insurance Act", "LAW"], ["TRIA", "ORG"], ["November 2002", "DATE"], ["TRIA", "ORG"], ["the end of 2007", "DATE"], ["2014", "DATE"], ["TRIA", "ORG"], ["Terrorism Risk", "WORK_OF_ART"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["Terrorism Risk and Insurance", "WORK_OF_ART"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["more than 75 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["the years", "DATE"], ["1997", "DATE"], ["$5 million to $25 million", "MONEY"]], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [["four", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [["$25 million", "MONEY"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["Hurricane Andrew", "EVENT"], ["1992", "DATE"], ["Northridge", "ORG"], ["1994", "DATE"], ["third", "ORDINAL"], ["the World Trade Center", "ORG"], ["2001", "DATE"], ["Hurricane Katrina", "EVENT"], ["2005", "DATE"], ["fourth", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [["Flood Insurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [["34", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["two", "CARDINAL"], ["First", "ORDINAL"], ["Second", "ORDINAL"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["New York", "GPE"], ["2001", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["January 2010", "DATE"], ["the National Safety Council", "ORG"], ["NSC", "ORG"], ["at least 1.6 million", "CARDINAL"], ["28 percent", "PERCENT"], ["each year", "DATE"], ["1.4 million", "CARDINAL"], ["200,000", "CARDINAL"], ["the National Highway Traffic Safety Administration", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["July 2009", "DATE"], ["Virginia Tech Transportation Institute", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["18 months", "DATE"], ["23", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["nearly five seconds", "TIME"], ["more than 100 yards", "QUANTITY"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t35Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 15}, {"entities": [], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["2009", "DATE"], ["Ceres", "ORG"], ["some 244", "CARDINAL"], ["29", "CARDINAL"], ["2008", "DATE"], ["190", "CARDINAL"], ["26", "CARDINAL"], ["2007", "DATE"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["26", "CARDINAL"], ["2007", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Global Warming", "PERSON"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["Insurers’ Contribution to Lowering Greenhouse Gases: Insurers", "ORG"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["years", "DATE"], ["36", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"], ["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["At least one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 15}, {"entities": [["New Products and Business Opportunities", "ORG"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["the end of the nineteenth century", "DATE"], ["the beginning of the twenty-first century", "DATE"], ["First", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["one ton", "QUANTITY"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["one ton", "QUANTITY"], ["The Kyoto Protocol", "LAW"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["Second", "ORDINAL"], ["more than 25 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["U.S.", "GPE"], ["more than 10 percent", "PERCENT"], ["Ceres", "ORG"], ["the Brookings Institution", "ORG"], ["about 8 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"], ["more miles per gallon", "QUANTITY"], ["PAYD", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["California", "GPE"], ["PAYD", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Green” Building Insurance Coverage:   ", "WORK_OF_ART"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["38", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["The Green Building Council", "ORG"], ["Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["LEED", "ORG"], ["2001", "DATE"], ["Ceres", "PERSON"], ["more than one-third", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["more than one-third", "CARDINAL"], ["more than 50 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [["the next few years", "DATE"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["2006", "DATE"]], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [], "topic": 12}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t39Auto InsuranceUpdates", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["decades", "DATE"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [["The Poor Economy Has Not Had a Negative Impact on", "ORG"], ["Credit Scores", "ORG"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [["April 2009", "DATE"], ["Property Casualty Insurers of America", "ORG"], ["Fair Isaac", "PERSON"], ["TransUnion", "ORG"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [["PCI", "ORG"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [["Federal Activities", "ORG"], ["The Federal Trade Commission", "ORG"], ["FTC", "ORG"], ["nine", "CARDINAL"], ["Fair", "ORG"], ["2003", "DATE"], ["FTC", "ORG"], ["the Office of Fair Housing", "ORG"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [["40", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [["2010", "DATE"], ["FTC", "ORG"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [["FTC", "ORG"], ["Credit-Based Insurance Scores", "ORG"], ["Consumers of Automobile Insurance", "ORG"], ["July 2007", "DATE"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Fair", "ORG"], ["2003", "DATE"], ["FTC", "ORG"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [["the General Accountability Office", "ORG"], ["Treasury", "ORG"], ["FTC", "ORG"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [["The Federal Reserve", "ORG"], ["the Federal Reserve", "ORG"], ["the end of August 2007", "DATE"], ["FTC", "ORG"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["760", "CARDINAL"], ["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["600", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [["Credit Report Information", "ORG"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["42", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["the United States", "GPE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["the United States", "GPE"], ["about 5,000", "CARDINAL"], ["each year", "DATE"], ["1900", "DATE"], ["39", "CARDINAL"], ["50", "CARDINAL"], ["One", "CARDINAL"], ["U.S.", "GPE"], ["the San Francisco Earthquake", "FAC"], ["1906", "DATE"], ["$96 billion", "MONEY"], ["AIR Worldwide", "ORG"]], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [["Northridge", "ORG"], ["Southern California", "LOC"], ["January", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["17, 1994", "DATE"], ["U.S.", "GPE"], ["an estimated $20 billion", "MONEY"], ["$12.5 billion", "MONEY"], ["the California Earthquake Authority", "ORG"], ["CEA", "ORG"], ["1996", "DATE"], ["Northridge", "PERSON"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["the California Legislature", "ORG"], ["CEA", "ORG"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["Only about 12 percent", "PERCENT"], ["Californians", "NORP"], ["about 30 percent", "PERCENT"], ["1996", "DATE"], ["1994", "DATE"], ["Californians", "NORP"], ["CEA", "ORG"], ["an average 22 percent", "PERCENT"], ["July 1, 2006", "DATE"], ["CEA", "ORG"], ["several years", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["44", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"], ["Major Recent Earthquakes", "ORG"], ["the beginning of 2010", "DATE"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["7.0", "CARDINAL"], ["Haiti", "GPE"], ["January", "DATE"], ["8.8", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Chile", "GPE"], ["February", "DATE"], ["Haiti", "GPE"], ["220,000", "CARDINAL"], ["$8 billion dollars", "MONEY"], ["Chile", "GPE"], ["Chile", "GPE"], ["Chile", "GPE"], ["over $4 billion", "MONEY"], ["more than $20 billion", "MONEY"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["more than $20 billion", "MONEY"], ["Munich Re", "PERSON"], ["about 500", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t45Auto InsuranceUpdates", "ORG"]], "topic": 15}, {"entities": [], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["the early and mid-1980s", "DATE"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["about 2001", "DATE"], ["early 2004", "DATE"], ["2010", "DATE"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["many years", "DATE"], ["the 1920s", "DATE"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["year", "DATE"], ["46", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["half", "CARDINAL"], ["only one", "CARDINAL"], ["the 1950s and 1960s", "DATE"], ["three-year", "DATE"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["three-year", "DATE"], ["the 1970s", "DATE"], ["1980s", "DATE"], ["only two", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["the mid-1970s", "DATE"], ["the mid-1980s", "DATE"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["the last decade", "DATE"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["the Mississippi River", "LOC"], ["the 1960s", "DATE"]], "topic": 15}, {"entities": [["1968", "DATE"], ["Congress", "ORG"], ["the National Flood Insurance Program", "ORG"], ["three", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["NFIP", "ORG"], ["Hurricane Katrina", "EVENT"], ["2005", "DATE"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["NFIP", "ORG"], ["Congress", "ORG"], ["NFIP", "ORG"], ["About 20,400", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["1969", "DATE"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["1973", "DATE"], ["only about one million", "CARDINAL"], ["1973", "DATE"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["NFIP", "ORG"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["1994", "DATE"], ["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["50 percent", "PERCENT"], ["2007", "DATE"], ["NFIP", "ORG"], ["48", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["less than five years", "DATE"], ["five to 15 years", "DATE"], ["The Federal Emergency Management Agency", "ORG"], ["FEMA", "ORG"], ["about 80 percent", "PERCENT"], ["annually", "DATE"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["FEMA", "ORG"], ["Homeland Security", "ORG"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["1983", "DATE"], ["Write Your Own", "WORK_OF_ART"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["Today", "DATE"], ["the Write-Your-Own", "FAC"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["NFIP", "ORG"], ["an average loss year", "DATE"], ["an extraordinary year", "DATE"], ["Hurricane Katrina", "EVENT"], ["NFIP", "ORG"], ["the U.S. Treasury", "ORG"], ["Hurricane Katrina", "EVENT"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["FEMA", "ORG"], ["thousands", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["annual", "DATE"], ["1 percent", "PERCENT"], ["26 percent", "PERCENT"], ["30-year", "DATE"], ["9 percent", "PERCENT"], ["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t49Auto InsuranceUpdates", "ORG"], ["the same period", "DATE"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["Ninety percent", "PERCENT"], ["NFIP", "ORG"], ["some 25", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["30 days", "DATE"], ["1993", "DATE"], ["7,800", "CARDINAL"], ["the last minute", "TIME"], ["$48 million", "MONEY"], ["only $625,000", "MONEY"], ["NFIP", "ORG"], ["four", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["2006", "DATE"], ["the American Institutes for Research", "ORG"], ["AIR", "ORG"], ["AIR", "ORG"], ["NFIP", "ORG"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["AIR", "ORG"], ["AIR", "ORG"], ["NFIP", "ORG"], ["Congressional", "NORP"], ["three", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["FEMA", "ORG"], ["2007", "DATE"], ["NFIP", "ORG"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["only 30 to 40", "CARDINAL"], ["January 2006", "DATE"], ["FEMA", "ORG"], ["annual", "DATE"], ["$750 million", "MONEY"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["about $4.6 billion", "MONEY"], ["between 1978 and 2004", "DATE"], ["AIR", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["50", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"], ["10 percent", "PERCENT"], ["about $30 billion", "MONEY"], ["Fraud", "GPE"]], "topic": 20}, {"entities": [["third", "ORDINAL"], ["41", "CARDINAL"], ["the District of", "GPE"]], "topic": 20}, {"entities": [["Columbia", "ORG"], ["more than one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 20}, {"entities": [], "topic": 20}, {"entities": [["Healthcare", "ORG"]], "topic": 20}, {"entities": [["the 1980s", "DATE"]], "topic": 20}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"], ["five", "CARDINAL"], ["Americans", "NORP"], ["the Coalition Against Insurance Fraud", "ORG"], ["2008", "DATE"], ["The Four Faces \nInsurance Topics  Updates", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t51Auto InsuranceUpdates", "ORG"]], "topic": 20}, {"entities": [["today", "DATE"], ["10 years before", "DATE"], ["the Insurance Research Council", "ORG"], ["Americans", "NORP"], ["previous years", "DATE"]], "topic": 20}, {"entities": [], "topic": 20}, {"entities": [["About 19", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Insurers’ Antifraud Measures", "ORG"]], "topic": 20}, {"entities": [["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 20}, {"entities": [], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["Property Casualty Insurers Association of America", "ORG"], ["FBI", "ORG"], ["National Insurance Crime Bureau", "ORG"], ["NICB", "ORG"], ["the International Association of Special Investigating Units", "ORG"], ["NICB", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["52", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"], ["Medical Malpractice", "ORG"], ["Medical Malpractice Insurance", "ORG"], ["the United States", "GPE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["$254.7 billion", "MONEY"], ["2008", "DATE"], ["838", "MONEY"], ["billions of dollars", "MONEY"], ["U.S.", "GPE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["the 1980s", "DATE"], ["U.S.", "GPE"], ["the last decade", "DATE"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["the early 2000s", "DATE"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["medi-cal", "ORG"], ["the National Conference of \nState Legislatures", "ORG"], ["30", "CARDINAL"], ["the Virgin Islands", "GPE"], ["Puerto Rico", "GPE"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["the past few years", "DATE"], ["Georgia", "GPE"], ["the Supreme Court", "ORG"], ["2005", "DATE"], ["350,000", "MONEY"], ["Carol Hunstein", "PERSON"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["I.I.I. \tInsurance \tHandbook", "ORG"], ["53", "CARDINAL"], ["Medical Malpractice", "ORG"], ["Illinois", "GPE"], ["the Supreme Court", "ORG"], ["2005", "DATE"], ["500,000", "MONEY"], ["1", "MONEY"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["Maryland", "GPE"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["Forums", "GPE"], ["more than 520,000", "CARDINAL"], ["2009", "DATE"], ["$2.5 billion", "MONEY"], ["$700 million", "MONEY"], ["More than 85 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["December 2009", "DATE"], ["the American Tort Reform \nAssociation (ATRA", "LAW"], ["annual", "DATE"], ["Judicial Hellholes", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["ATRA", "PERSON"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["ATRA", "PERSON"], ["six", "CARDINAL"], ["Judicial Hellholes", "ORG"], ["South Florida", "LOC"], ["West Virginia", "GPE"], ["Cook County", "GPE"], ["Illinois", "GPE"], ["Atlantic County", "GPE"], ["New Jersey", "GPE"], ["New Mexico", "GPE"], ["New York \nCity", "GPE"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["54", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["Bangladeshi Nobel Prize", "PERSON"], ["Muhammad Yunus", "PERSON"], ["millions", "CARDINAL"], ["Asia", "LOC"], ["Africa", "LOC"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["Asia", "LOC"], ["Africa", "LOC"], ["American International Group Inc.", "ORG"], ["AIG", "ORG"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["Uganda", "GPE"], ["1997", "DATE"], ["Swiss", "NORP"], ["Munich Re", "PERSON"], ["Allianz", "ORG"], ["Zurich Financial Services", "ORG"], ["2005", "DATE"], ["Indonesia", "GPE"], ["2010", "DATE"], ["Haiti", "GPE"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["2009", "DATE"], ["Swiss", "NORP"], ["2008", "DATE"], ["Latin America", "LOC"], ["Central", "ORG"], ["Eastern Europe", "LOC"], ["South", "LOC"], ["East Asia", "LOC"], ["the Middle East", "LOC"], ["Israel", "GPE"], ["Central Asia", "LOC"], ["Turkey", "GPE"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["Israel", "GPE"], ["Central Asia", "LOC"], ["Turkey", "GPE"], ["Africa", "LOC"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["2009", "DATE"], ["the International Association of Insurance Supervisors", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["the International Labor Organization", "ORG"], ["the “Access to Insurance Initiative", "ORG"], ["2009", "DATE"], ["60", "CARDINAL"], ["the Fifth International Microinsurance Conference", "ORG"], ["Munich Re", "PERSON"], ["the Microinsurance Network", "ORG"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t55Auto InsuranceUpdates", "ORG"], ["four", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["the days", "DATE"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["12", "CARDINAL"], ["Puerto Rico", "GPE"], ["Florida", "GPE"], ["Michigan", "GPE"], ["New Jersey", "GPE"], ["New York", "GPE"], ["Pennsylvania", "GPE"], ["seven", "CARDINAL"], ["Hawaii", "GPE"], ["Kansas", "GPE"], ["Kentucky", "GPE"], ["Massachusetts", "GPE"], ["Minnesota", "GPE"], ["North Dakota", "GPE"], ["Utah", "GPE"], ["Three", "CARDINAL"], ["New Jersey", "GPE"], ["Pennsylvania", "GPE"], ["Kentucky", "GPE"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["56", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["third", "ORDINAL"], ["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["New Jersey", "GPE"], ["Pennsylvania", "GPE"], ["Ken", "PERSON"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["U.S.", "GPE"], ["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["insurance—$2.50", "ORG"], ["1,000", "MONEY"], ["150,000", "MONEY"], ["150 x $", "MONEY"], ["2.50", "MONEY"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["three", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["58", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["U.S.", "GPE"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["2009", "DATE"], ["Congress", "ORG"], ["fed", "ORG"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["fed", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Georgia", "GPE"], ["May 2008", "DATE"], ["Georgia", "GPE"], ["at least 30", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["Flex Rating", "PERSON"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t59Auto InsuranceUpdates", "ORG"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["60", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["about 9 percent", "PERCENT"], ["U.S.", "GPE"], ["2008", "DATE"], ["the Reinsurance Association of America", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["Hurricane Andrew", "EVENT"], ["Southern Florida", "LOC"], ["1992", "DATE"], ["$15.5 billion", "MONEY"], ["U.S.", "GPE"], ["Hurricane Andrew", "EVENT"], ["$8 billion", "MONEY"]], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Hurricane Andrew", "EVENT"], ["the Florida Windstorm Association", "ORG"], ["1996", "DATE"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["U.S.", "GPE"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["1997", "DATE"], ["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t61Auto InsuranceUpdates", "ORG"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["years", "DATE"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["U.S. Treasuries", "ORG"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["one-year", "DATE"], ["three", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["each year", "DATE"], ["multibillion dollar", "MONEY"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["multibillion dollar", "MONEY"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["62", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["The Automobile Residual Market", "ORG"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["New Hampshire", "GPE"], ["1938", "DATE"], ["Today", "DATE"], ["50", "CARDINAL"], ["the District of Columbia", "GPE"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["four", "CARDINAL"], ["four", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t63Auto InsuranceUpdates", "ORG"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["42", "CARDINAL"], ["the District of Columbia", "GPE"], ["Massachu-setts", "PERSON"], ["three-year", "DATE"], ["April 2008", "DATE"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["a given day", "DATE"], ["100", "CARDINAL"], ["10 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["10", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["Joint Underwriting Associations", "ORG"], ["four", "CARDINAL"], ["Florida", "GPE"], ["Hawaii", "GPE"], ["Michigan", "GPE"], ["Missouri", "GPE"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["JUA", "ORG"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["JUA", "ORG"], ["Michigan", "GPE"], ["JUA", "ORG"], ["JUA", "ORG"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["64", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["North Carolina", "GPE"], ["New \nHampshire", "GPE"], ["Massachusetts", "GPE"], ["Massachusetts", "GPE"], ["April 2008", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Commonwealth Automobile Insurers", "ORG"], ["CAR", "ORG"], ["three-year", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"], ["Maryland", "GPE"], ["1973", "DATE"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["the Maryland Automobile Insurance Fund", "ORG"], ["years", "DATE"], ["Maryland", "GPE"], ["the Auto Insurance Market: \n Together", "ORG"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["about 1.97 million", "CARDINAL"], ["2007", "DATE"], ["about 1.06 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["9.0 percent", "PERCENT"], ["2006", "DATE"], ["the Automobile Insurance Plans Service Office", "ORG"], ["1990", "DATE"], ["6.3 percent", "PERCENT"], ["2007", "DATE"], ["the 1990s", "DATE"], ["only one", "CARDINAL"], ["North Carolina", "GPE"], ["more than a million", "CARDINAL"], ["1.5 million", "CARDINAL"], ["more than 21.6 percent", "PERCENT"], ["South Carolina", "GPE"], ["1998", "DATE"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["1998", "DATE"], ["38 percent", "PERCENT"], ["1996", "DATE"], ["close to zero", "CARDINAL"], ["2007", "DATE"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["The Property Residual Market\nPools", "ORG"], ["Beach", "PERSON"], ["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["redistrib", "NORP"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["Beach", "LOC"], ["Thirty-two", "CARDINAL"], ["the District of Columbia", "GPE"], ["FAIR", "ORG"], ["Fair Access", "ORG"], ["Insur-", "GPE"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["Requirements Plans", "PERSON"], ["FAIR", "ORG"], ["Congress", "ORG"], ["the Housing and Urban Development Act", "ORG"], ["1968", "DATE"], ["1967", "DATE"], ["One", "CARDINAL"], ["Arkansas", "GPE"], ["1988", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Mississippi", "GPE"], ["2003", "DATE"], ["Plan", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Georgia", "GPE"], ["Massachusetts", "GPE"], ["New York", "GPE"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["Atlantic", "LOC"], ["Gulf Coasts", "ORG"], ["between 1969 and 1971", "DATE"], ["Beach", "PERSON"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["66", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"], ["FAIR Plans", "ORG"], ["Plans", "NORP"], ["five", "CARDINAL"], ["Alabama", "GPE"], ["Mississippi", "GPE"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["South Carolina", "GPE"], ["North Carolina", "GPE"], ["Texas", "GPE"], ["2001", "DATE"], ["seven", "CARDINAL"], ["Florida", "GPE"], ["2002", "DATE"], ["2003", "DATE"], ["Louisiana", "GPE"], ["Plans", "NORP"], ["Alabama", "GPE"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["WindMap", "ORG"], ["New Jersey", "GPE"], ["Mississippi", "GPE"], ["South Carolina", "GPE"], ["Texas", "GPE"], ["Alabama", "GPE"], ["North Carolina", "GPE"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["Beach", "PERSON"], ["Plan", "EVENT"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"], ["Beach", "LOC"], ["the National Flood \nInsurance Program", "ORG"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["Beach", "PERSON"], ["FAIR Plans", "ORG"], ["New York State", "GPE"], ["Florida", "GPE"], ["Louisiana", "GPE"], ["FAIR", "ORG"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["Louisiana", "GPE"], ["FAIR", "ORG"], ["Texas", "GPE"], ["earlier years", "DATE"], ["FAIR", "ORG"], ["New York", "GPE"], ["Massachusetts", "GPE"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["2002", "DATE"], ["Florida", "GPE"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["JUA", "ORG"], ["the Florida Windstorm Underwriting Association", "ORG"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["the Citizens’ Property Insurance Corporation", "LAW"], ["CPIC", "ORG"], ["The Florida", "ORG"], ["CPIC", "NORP"], ["Citizens", "ORG"], ["the years", "DATE"], ["hundreds of millions of dollars", "MONEY"], ["Louisiana", "GPE"], ["Florida", "GPE"], ["the FAIR Plan", "LAW"], ["the Louisiana Citizens Property", "ORG"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["Citizens Property Insur-ance Corporation", "ORG"], ["2004", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["the 1970s or", "DATE"], ["1980s", "DATE"], ["MAP", "ORG"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["East Coast", "LOC"], ["Connecticut", "GPE"], ["Texas", "GPE"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["Pools", "PERSON"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["four", "CARDINAL"], ["North Dakota", "GPE"], ["Ohio", "GPE"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["Wyoming", "GPE"], ["July 2008", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["68", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 15}, {"entities": [["Second", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["the Americans With Disabilities Act", "LAW"], ["Second", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["second", "ORDINAL"], ["Workers Compensation Commission", "ORG"], ["Industrial Board or", "ORG"], ["Department of Labor", "ORG"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["September 11", "DATE"], ["about $31.6 billion", "MONEY"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["Congress", "ORG"], ["the Terrorism Risk Insurance Act", "ORG"], ["TRIA", "ORG"], ["TRIA", "ORG"], ["November 26, 2002", "DATE"], ["two years", "DATE"], ["December 2005", "DATE"], ["TRIA", "ORG"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["TRIA", "ORG"], ["another seven years to 2014", "DATE"], ["December 2007", "DATE"], ["the Terrorism Risk Insurance Program Reauthorization Act", "ORG"], ["2007", "DATE"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["100,000 miles", "QUANTITY"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["70", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 15}, {"entities": [], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["AIR Worldwide", "ORG"]], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [], "topic": 19}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["the United States", "GPE"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["the Terrorism Risk Insurance Act", "LAW"], ["TRIA", "ORG"], ["TRIA", "ORG"], ["2005", "DATE"], ["2007", "DATE"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["the U.S. Government Accountability Office", "ORG"], ["Working Group on Financial Markets", "ORG"], ["September 2006", "DATE"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["NBCR", "ORG"], ["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t71Auto InsuranceUpdates", "ORG"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["Working Group", "ORG"], ["TRIA", "ORG"], ["TRIA", "ORG"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["TRIA", "ORG"], ["2007", "DATE"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["the United States", "GPE"], ["Treasury", "ORG"], ["State", "ORG"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["2005", "DATE"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["September 11", "DATE"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["72", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"], ["the Federal Victims Compensation Act", "ORG"], ["nearly $7 billion", "MONEY"], ["September 11", "DATE"], ["TRIA", "ORG"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["Mandated Coverages/Exclusions", "ORG"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["Texas", "GPE"], ["www.iii.org/issues_updates\n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t73Auto InsuranceUpdates", "ORG"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["the late 1980s", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["The Workers Compensation Social Contract", "ORG"], ["the United States", "GPE"], ["the 19th century", "DATE"], ["the early 1900s", "DATE"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["Wisconsin", "GPE"], ["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["1911", "DATE"], ["New York", "GPE"], ["a year earlier", "DATE"], ["1920", "DATE"], ["eight", "CARDINAL"], ["1949", "DATE"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["74", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"], ["1972", "DATE"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["the National Commission on State Workmen’s Compensation Laws", "ORG"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["the National Commission’s", "ORG"], ["19", "CARDINAL"], ["1972", "DATE"], ["fewer than five", "CARDINAL"], ["four", "CARDINAL"], ["three", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["the Longshoremen’s and Harbor Workers Compensation Act", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["1927", "DATE"], ["1984", "DATE"], ["the Federal Employees’ Compensation Act", "ORG"], ["U.S.", "GPE"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["14", "CARDINAL"], ["four", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Texas", "GPE"], ["about one-third", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["more than one-third", "CARDINAL"], ["About nine", "CARDINAL"], ["10", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t75Auto InsuranceUpdates", "ORG"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["the first day", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Impairment", "PERSON"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["the American Medical Association’s", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["weeks", "DATE"], ["weekly", "DATE"], ["several days", "DATE"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["the mid-1950s", "DATE"], ["an average 0.5 percent", "PERCENT"], ["1970", "DATE"], ["1 percent", "PERCENT"], ["the 1980s and", "DATE"], ["1990s", "DATE"], ["1994", "DATE"], ["2.99 percent", "PERCENT"], ["76", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tInsurance Topics  Updates", "ORG"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["John Burton", "PERSON"], ["Policy Review", "ORG"], ["January/February 2008", "DATE"], ["2007", "DATE"], ["2.28", "CARDINAL"], ["10-year", "DATE"], ["1.92", "CARDINAL"], ["2001", "DATE"], ["NCCI", "GPE"], ["2008", "DATE"], ["1.7 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["several hundred", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["the 1980s", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["more than a dozen", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["today", "DATE"], ["5 to 10 percent", "PERCENT"], ["as much as 20 percent", "PERCENT"], ["roughly a third", "CARDINAL"], ["12 to 15 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t77Auto InsuranceUpdates", "ORG"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["About one-half", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["NCCI", "GPE"], ["29", "CARDINAL"], ["Terrorism Coverage: Since", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["September 11, 2001", "DATE"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["Risk Man-agement", "PERSON"], ["San Francisco", "GPE"], ["1906", "DATE"], ["today", "DATE"], ["as many as 78,000", "CARDINAL"], ["5,000", "CARDINAL"], ["over $7 billion", "MONEY"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["$300,000 to", "MONEY"], ["$1 million", "MONEY"], ["New York", "GPE"], ["Arizona", "GPE"], ["Maryland", "GPE"], ["Oregon", "GPE"], ["North Dakota", "GPE"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["Arizona", "GPE"], ["Maryland", "GPE"], ["Oregon", "GPE"], ["North Dakota", "GPE"], ["California", "GPE"], ["Minnesota", "GPE"], ["Pennsylvania", "GPE"], ["Ohio", "GPE"], ["Colorado", "GPE"], ["Montana", "GPE"], ["Texas", "GPE"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["Idaho New York Utah", "ORG"], ["Kentucky", "GPE"], ["Oklahoma", "GPE"], ["Virginia", "GPE"], ["2013", "DATE"], ["78", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["each year", "DATE"], ["403(B", "CARDINAL"], ["the United States", "GPE"], ["529", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["the Internal Revenue", "ORG"], ["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["LOMA’s Glossary of Insurance and Financial Services Terms", "ORG"], ["2002", "DATE"], ["LL Global", "ORG"], ["LL Global", "ORG"], ["U.S.", "GPE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Glossary", "PERSON"], ["LOMA", "ORG"], ["LL Global", "ORG"], ["LOMA’s", "ORG"], ["Handbook", "PERSON"], ["LL Global, Inc.", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["LOMA", "ORG"], ["LL Global", "ORG"], ["Handbook", "PERSON"], ["LL Global", "ORG"], ["Handbook", "PERSON"], ["Glossary", "PERSON"], ["LL Global", "ORG"], ["the LOMA Glossary", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Handbook", "PERSON"], ["LL Global", "ORG"], ["LL Global", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["LL Global", "ORG"], ["Handbook", "PERSON"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["ACCIDENT AND HEALTH INSURANCE\nCoverage for accidental injury", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["two", "CARDINAL"], ["DIVIDEND", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Replace-", "PERSON"], ["ACTUARY", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Extra", "NORP"], ["one-year", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["fifth", "ORDINAL"], ["80", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Generic", "ORG"], ["AGENCY", "ORG"], ["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["only one", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["Commutative", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["ADR", "ORG"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["third", "ORDINAL"], ["third", "ORDINAL"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["ANNUAL", "DATE"], ["a particular year", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["ANNUITY", "ORG"], ["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["about \na year", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["ANNUITY", "ORG"], ["ANNUITY", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["ANNUITY", "ORG"], ["Gross", "PERSON"], ["82", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["ANNUITY", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["ANNUITY", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["the McCarran-Ferguson Act", "FAC"], ["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["third", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["more than 90 days", "DATE"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["six", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["Personal Injury \nProtection", "ORG"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["4", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["5", "CARDINAL"], ["6", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["years", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["See Insurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [["5 to 7 percent", "PERCENT"], ["the \nfirst year", "DATE"], ["zero", "CARDINAL"], ["5", "CARDINAL"], ["7 \nyears", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["84", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["The Federal Reserve", "ORG"], ["the \nComptroller of the Currency", "ORG"], ["FDIC", "ORG"], ["BASIS", "ORG"], ["0.01 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["0.01 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["FAIR", "ORG"], ["Residual market)*BENEFICIARY", "PERSON"], ["See Annuity", "ORG"], ["more than one", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["more than one", "CARDINAL"], ["Equipment Breakdown", "PERSON"], ["Breakdown", "PERSON"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook", "ORG"], ["Standard & Poor’s", "ORG"], ["Moody’s \nInvestors Service", "ORG"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["BURGLARY", "ORG"], ["BUSINESS INCOME INSURANCE", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["BUSINESS INCOME INSURANCE\nCommercial", "ORG"]], "topic": 21}, {"entities": [["two or more weeks", "DATE"]], "topic": 21}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["the World Trade Center", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Policyholder", "PERSON"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["86", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["Main Street", "FAC"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["Main Street", "FAC"], ["Solvency", "ORG"], ["only one", "CARDINAL"], ["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["CAR YEAR\nEqual", "ORG"], ["to 365 days", "DATE"], ["OPTION", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Nonforfeiture", "GPE"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["$25 million", "MONEY"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["40-year", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["multibillion dollar", "MONEY"], ["thousands", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Hurricane Andrew", "EVENT"], ["the World Trade Center", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["The \nAmerican College", "ORG"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["CHARTERED LIFE \nUNDERWRITER/CLU", "ORG"], ["the \nAmerican Institute for Chartered Property \nCasualty Underwriters", "ORG"], ["three years", "DATE"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["Consolidated Omnibus Budget \nReconciliation Act", "ORG"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["20", "CARDINAL"], ["18 months", "DATE"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["88", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["20 percent", "PERCENT"], ["20 percent", "PERCENT"], ["80 percent", "PERCENT"], ["100 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["100 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["LIABILITY INSURANCE/CGL", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["fidelity", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["Premiums", "NORP"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["Generic", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["See Primary", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["90", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["CREDIT LIFE INSURANCE\nLife", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [["See Insurance", "ORG"], ["CI", "ORG"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["DEDUCTIBLE", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["years", "DATE"], ["the final years", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["DEPENDENT LIFE INSURANCE\nSee Family", "ORG"], ["INSTITUTION", "ORG"], ["92", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["DIRECTORS", "PERSON"], ["LIABILITY INSURANCE/D&O\nDirectors", "ORG"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["weekly", "DATE"], ["monthly", "DATE"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["OPTION", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["See Accidental", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Information System", "ORG"], ["IRIS", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["days", "DATE"], ["Fidelity", "ORG"], ["EMPLOYER", "ORG"], ["LIABILITY", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["EMPLOYER", "ORG"], ["LIABILITY", "ORG"], ["94", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["EQUITY", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["EQUITY", "ORG"], ["EQUITY", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["ERRORS", "ORG"], ["monthly", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["only one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["EXTENDED REPLACEMENT", "GPE"], ["120 percent", "PERCENT"], ["125 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"], ["529", "CARDINAL"], ["78", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["78", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["FAIR ACCESS TO INSURANCE \nREQUIREMENTS", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["28", "CARDINAL"], ["the District of Columbia", "GPE"]], "topic": 18}, {"entities": [["96", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["overnight", "TIME"], ["FEDERAL INSURANCE \nADMINISTRATION/", "ORG"], ["the National Flood Insurance Program", "ORG"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["the National Flood Insurance Program", "ORG"], ["FEDERAL RESERVE BOARD", "ORG"], ["Seven", "CARDINAL"], ["U.S.", "GPE"], ["FIDELITY", "ORG"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["FIRE INSURANCE\nCoverage", "ORG"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["FIRST-PARTY COVERAGE\nCoverage", "ORG"], ["Third", "ORDINAL"], ["ANNUITY", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["Third", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["FLOOD INSURANCE\nCoverage", "ORG"], ["Flood Insurance Program", "ORG"], ["FORCED PLACE INSURANCE\nInsurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 20}, {"entities": [["up to one month", "DATE"], ["98", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["FREQUENCY", "ORG"], ["One", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["Separate", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["the Securities and Exchange \nCommission", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["OEM", "ORG"], ["OEM", "ORG"], ["Competi-", "ORG"], ["1", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["three", "CARDINAL"], ["annual", "DATE"], ["every three years", "DATE"], ["DRIVER", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Financial", "ORG"], ["Congress", "ORG"], ["1999", "DATE"], ["Depression", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["GI", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["GI", "ORG"], ["GIO", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["100", "CARDINAL"], ["third", "ORDINAL"], ["50", "CARDINAL"], ["the District of Co-\nlumbia", "GPE"], ["Puerto Rico", "GPE"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["LIABILITY", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["third", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["HOUSE", "ORG"], ["to 365 days", "DATE"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["ANNUITY", "ORG"], ["IDENTITY THEFT INSURANCE\nCoverage", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["101Glossary", "CARDINAL"], ["ANNUITY", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["about a year", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["Time", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["years", "DATE"], ["decades", "DATE"], ["IBNR", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["102", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Typical-\nly", "PERSON"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Roth", "PERSON"], ["1997", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Float-", "PERSON"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Floater", "PERSON"], ["INSOLVENCY", "GPE"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["three", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["103Glossary", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["See Beach", "GPE"], ["Fair", "ORG"], ["FAIR", "ORG"], ["Joint", "ORG"], ["the \nNational Association of Insurance", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["IRIS", "ORG"]], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [], "topic": 11}, {"entities": [["two", "CARDINAL"], ["twenty-four", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["Surrender", "PERSON"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["104", "ORG"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["two", "CARDINAL"], ["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["BB", "GPE"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["Less than 2 percent", "PERCENT"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["two", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["two", "CARDINAL"], ["K\nKEY PERSON INSURANCE\nInsurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["105Glossary", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["Premiums", "PERSON"], ["each year", "DATE"], ["Single", "LOC"], ["LIABILITY INSURANCE\nInsurance", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["See Life", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["See Life", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["See Life", "ORG"], ["LIMITED PAYMENT LIFE INSURANCE\nLife", "ORG"], ["20 years", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["20 years", "DATE"], ["106", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["the Federal Bankruptcy Code", "LAW"], ["LIQUIDITY", "PERSON"], ["LIQUOR LIABILITY\nCoverage", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["LLOYD", "ORG"], ["LONDON", "GPE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Lloyd’s", "ORG"], ["Lloyd’s", "PERSON"], ["London", "GPE"], ["the 1600s", "DATE"], ["Lloyd’s", "ORG"], ["Names", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["the \n1990s", "DATE"], ["LLOYDS", "ORG"]], "topic": 17}, {"entities": [["LLOYDS\nCorporation", "ORG"], ["Lloyd’s", "ORG"], ["London", "GPE"], ["Texas", "GPE"], ["daily", "DATE"]], "topic": 17}, {"entities": [["daily", "DATE"], ["LTC", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t107Glossary", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["MANAGED CARE\nArrangement", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Wear", "PERSON"], ["See Inland", "ORG"], ["Ocean", "ORG"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["3", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["1945", "DATE"], ["third", "ORDINAL"], ["between \ntwo", "CARDINAL"], ["MEDICAID", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["1965", "DATE"], ["108", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["MIB", "ORG"], ["See Malpractice", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["MEDICARE", "ORG"], ["65 or", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Medicare", "ORG"], ["MIB", "ORG"], ["Medical \nInformation Bureau", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["2", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["Single", "LOC"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["the Federal Reserve", "ORG"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["PMI", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["early days", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["MUNICIPAL LIABILITY INSURANCE", "ORG"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["110", "CARDINAL"], ["Peril", "PERSON"], ["NATIONAL FLOOD \nINSURANCE PROGRAM\nFederal government", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Flood", "ORG"], ["Gross", "PERSON"], ["See Annuity", "ORG"]], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["See Annuity", "ORG"], ["20-year", "DATE"], ["Surrender", "PERSON"], ["Premiums", "PERSON"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["10,000", "MONEY"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["includ-\ning", "PERSON"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["age 65", "DATE"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook", "ORG"], ["the United States", "GPE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["NURSING HOME INSURANCE", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["many years later", "DATE"]], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["includ-\ning", "PERSON"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["ORDINARY LIFE INSURANCE\n", "ORG"], ["112", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["the New York Stock \nExchange", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["the 1990s", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["PAYD", "ORG"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["2", "CARDINAL"], ["3", "CARDINAL"], ["4", "CARDINAL"], ["See Life", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["See Life", "ORG"], ["the Pension Plan Termi-\nnation Insurance", "LAW"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["the \n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["CAPITA BENEFICIARY \nDESIGNATION", "FAC"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["only one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["DESIGNATION", "GPE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["See Annuity", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["See Additional", "ORG"], ["Dividend", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["114", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["ten", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["1", "CARDINAL"], ["the three months", "DATE"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["first", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["two \nyears", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["annually", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["first", "ORDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t115Glossary", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [["See Mortgage", "ORG"], ["the \nSecurities and Exchange Commission", "ORG"], ["LIABILITY", "ORG"]], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [["PROPERTY/CASUALTY INSURANCE\nCovers", "ORG"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["the United States", "GPE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["the 1950s and 1960s", "DATE"], ["three year", "DATE"], ["103", "CARDINAL"], ["November 1988", "DATE"], ["California", "GPE"]], "topic": 16}, {"entities": [["November 1988", "DATE"], ["California", "GPE"], ["more than a decade", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["116", "CARDINAL"], ["monthly", "DATE"], ["quarterly", "DATE"], ["annually", "DATE"], ["PURE LIFE ANNUITY", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["1,000", "MONEY"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["A.M. Best Co.", "ORG"], ["Fitch, Inc.", "ORG"], ["Moody’s", "ORG"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["A.M. Best Co.", "ORG"], ["Fitch, Inc.", "ORG"], ["Moody’s \nInvestors Services", "ORG"], ["Standard & Poor’s Corp.", "ORG"], ["Weiss Ratings, Inc. Factors", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["100,000", "CARDINAL"], ["ten.", "DATE"], ["Years \nago", "DATE"], ["Today", "DATE"]], "topic": 4}, {"entities": [["broad loss data", "ORG"], ["ISO", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["National", "ORG"], ["Securities Dealers", "ORG"], ["NASD", "ORG"], ["24", "CARDINAL"], ["26", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["24", "CARDINAL"], ["26", "CARDINAL"], ["National", "ORG"], ["Securities Dealers", "ORG"], ["NASD", "ORG"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["NASD", "ORG"], ["NASD", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["third", "ORDINAL"], ["Posses-", "PERSON"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["Posses-", "PERSON"]], "topic": 10}, {"entities": [["118", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\tGlossary", "ORG"], ["U.S.", "GPE"], ["the Federal Reserve", "ORG"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["20 percent to 25 percent", "PERCENT"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["FAIR Plans", "ORG"]], "topic": 7}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["RISK MANAGEMENT\nManagement of the varied risks", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 9}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["RISK-BASED CAPITAL", "ORG"], ["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["the \n\t I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t119Glossary", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["SECOND", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["SECOND-TO-DIE LIFE INSURANCE\n", "DATE"], ["the United States", "GPE"], ["Section 1035", "LAW"], ["the Internal \nRevenue Code", "ORG"], ["415", "CARDINAL"], ["the Internal Revenue Code", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Section 415", "LAW"], ["the Internal Revenue Service", "ORG"], ["annually", "DATE"], ["SEC", "ORG"], ["SEC", "ORG"], ["annual", "DATE"], ["10", "CARDINAL"], ["quarterly", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["10", "CARDINAL"], ["quarterly", "DATE"], ["10", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["Catastrophe", "PERSON"], ["Canada", "GPE"], ["Separate", "PERSON"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["120", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["the United States", "GPE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["3", "CARDINAL"], ["4", "CARDINAL"], ["See Life", "ORG"], ["One", "CARDINAL"], ["SEWER BACKUP COVERAGE", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["SEWER BACKUP COVERAGE\n", "ORG"], ["one to five years", "DATE"], ["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["one", "CARDINAL"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["several years", "DATE"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["SPIA", "ORG"], ["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["SOLVENCY\nInsurance", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["European Union", "ORG"], ["2012", "DATE"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["Criti", "GPE"], ["CI", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["SAP", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["SAP", "ORG"], ["SAP", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["See Life", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["See Annuity", "ORG"], ["122", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["1980", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["Liability Act", "LAW"], ["three", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["ond party", "ORG"], ["third", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": 14}, {"entities": [["See Capital", "ORG"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["five to seven", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["pare insurance policies", "ORG"], ["20-year", "DATE"], ["SURVIVORSHIP LIFE INSURANCE", "ORG"], ["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["TSA", "ORG"], ["the United States", "GPE"], ["the U.S. Internal Revenue Code", "ORG"], ["TEN-DAY FREE", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["five", "CARDINAL"], ["10", "CARDINAL"], ["20 \nyears", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["September 11", "DATE"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["The Terrorism Risk Insur-", "LAW"], ["TRIA", "ORG"], ["Congress", "ORG"], ["2002", "DATE"], ["two years", "DATE"], ["2005", "DATE"], ["THIRD-PARTY ADMINISTRATOR\nOutside", "ORG"], ["THIRD-PARTY COVERAGE\nLiability", "ORG"]], "topic": 13}, {"entities": [["third", "ORDINAL"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["second", "ORDINAL"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["124", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 2}, {"entities": [], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["TREASURY", "ORG"], ["U.S.", "GPE"], ["Treasury", "ORG"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["Treasury", "ORG"], ["three", "CARDINAL"], ["Treasury", "ORG"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["See Misrepresentation", "ORG"], ["125Glossary", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["n’t", "GPE"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["n’t", "GPE"], ["UNEARNED", "ORG"]], "topic": 8}, {"entities": [["UNIVERSAL LIFE INSURANCE", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["annual", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["126", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["VARIABLE LIFE INSURANCE", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["One", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["VOLATILITY", "ORG"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [["WAIVER", "PERSON"], ["DISABILITY", "ORG"], ["WP", "ORG"]], "topic": 3}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["15 days", "DATE"]], "topic": -1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 6}, {"entities": [["the day", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [], "topic": 5}, {"entities": [["Premiums", "PERSON"], ["The National Association of Insurance \nCommissioner", "ORG"], ["March 1999", "DATE"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["One-year", "DATE"], ["annually", "DATE"], ["ART", "ORG"], ["128", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 1}, {"entities": [["AMERICAN INSURANCE \nASSOCIATION", "ORG"], ["2101", "DATE"], ["L Street", "EVENT"], ["Suite", "PERSON"], ["400", "CARDINAL"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["20037Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["AMERICAN INSURANCE \nASSOCIATION", "ORG"], ["MID-ATLANTIC", "LOC"], ["2101", "DATE"], ["L Street", "EVENT"], ["400", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["2101", "DATE"], ["L Street", "FAC"], ["Suite", "PERSON"], ["400", "CARDINAL"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["www.aiadc.orgAMERICAN INSURANCE \nASSOCIATION", "ORG"], ["150", "CARDINAL"], ["Suite", "PERSON"], ["2525", "DATE"], ["Chicago", "GPE"], ["312-782", "CARDINAL"], ["312", "CARDINAL"], ["AMERICAN INSURANCE \nASSOCIATION", "ORG"], ["NORTHEAST", "LOC"], ["ALBANY", "ORG"], ["95", "CARDINAL"], ["Columbia Street \nAlbany", "FAC"], ["518", "CARDINAL"], ["518", "CARDINAL"], ["AMERICAN INSURANCE \nASSOCIATION", "ORG"], ["NORTHEAST", "LOC"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["NORTHEAST", "LOC"], ["1", "CARDINAL"], ["Walnut Street", "GPE"], ["Boston", "GPE"], ["MA 02108Tel", "FAC"], ["617", "CARDINAL"], ["617", "CARDINAL"], ["Directories\n\t ", "ORG"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t129Directories\nAMERICAN INSURANCE \nASSOCIATION", "ORG"], ["SOUTHEAST", "NORP"], ["5605", "DATE"], ["Glenridge Drive", "PERSON"], ["845", "CARDINAL"], ["Atlanta", "GPE"], ["30342Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["404", "CARDINAL"], ["404", "CARDINAL"], ["AMERICAN INSURANCE \nASSOCIATION", "ORG"], ["500 West 13th", "DATE"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["500", "CARDINAL"], ["Austin", "PERSON"], ["512", "CARDINAL"], ["512", "CARDINAL"], ["AMERICAN INSURANCE \nASSOCIATION", "ORG"], ["915", "CARDINAL"], ["L Street", "LOC"], ["1480", "DATE"], ["Sacramento", "GPE"], ["916", "CARDINAL"], ["916", "CARDINAL"], ["127", "CARDINAL"], ["Peyton Street", "GPE"], ["Alexandria", "GPE"], ["22314Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["800-221-7917Fax", "CARDINAL"], ["703", "CARDINAL"], ["INSTITUTE FOR BUSINESS \n& HOME SAFETY", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["INSTITUTE FOR BUSINESS \n& HOME SAFETY", "ORG"], ["Tampa", "GPE"], ["33617Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["813-286-3400Fax", "CARDINAL"], ["813-286-9960Web", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.", "ORG"], ["110 William Street", "PERSON"], ["New York", "GPE"], ["10038 Tel", "PERSON"], ["212", "CARDINAL"], ["212", "CARDINAL"], ["www.iii.orgA", "PERSON"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["I.I.I.", "ORG"], ["Florida", "GPE"], ["Lynne McChristian", "PERSON"], ["4775 E. Fowler AvenueTampa", "PERSON"], ["Florida", "GPE"], ["813-480-", "QUANTITY"], ["813-915-", "QUANTITY"], ["NETWORK", "ORG"], ["CALIFORNIA", "GPE"], ["Suite", "PERSON"], ["1610", "CARDINAL"], ["Los Angeles", "GPE"], ["213", "CARDINAL"], ["www.iinc.org\nINSURANCE RESEARCH COUNCIL", "ORG"], ["THE AMERICAN INSTITUTE FOR CPCU", "ORG"], ["PO Box", "ORG"], ["3025", "DATE"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["718", "CARDINAL"], ["Providence Road", "FAC"], ["PO Box", "ORG"], ["610", "CARDINAL"], ["610", "CARDINAL"], ["the American Institute for CPCU", "ORG"], ["130", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"], ["545", "CARDINAL"], ["Washington Blvd", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["ISO", "ORG"], ["545", "CARDINAL"], ["Washington Blvd", "ORG"], ["Jersey City", "GPE"], ["NJ", "ORG"], ["07310-1686", "DATE"], ["800-888-4476Fax", "QUANTITY"], ["201", "CARDINAL"], ["NATIONAL ASSOCIATION \nOF INSURANCE AND FINANCIAL ADVISORS\n", "ORG"], ["2901", "DATE"], ["Telestar Court", "ORG"], ["PO Box", "ORG"], ["12012", "DATE"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["2901", "DATE"], ["Telestar Court", "ORG"], ["PO Box 12012", "ORG"], ["Falls Church", "ORG"], ["VA", "GPE"], ["703", "CARDINAL"], ["NATIONAL ASSOCIATION \nOF MUTUAL INSURANCE COMPANIES", "ORG"], ["NAMIC", "PERSON"], ["PO Box 68700", "PERSON"], ["Indianapolis", "GPE"], ["46268Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["317", "CARDINAL"], ["317", "CARDINAL"], ["NAMIC", "PERSON"], ["WASHINGTON", "GPE"], ["DC", "GPE"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["NAMIC", "PERSON"], ["WASHINGTON", "GPE"], ["DC", "GPE"], ["122", "CARDINAL"], ["540", "CARDINAL"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["www.namic.org NATIONAL ASSOCIATION \nOF PROFESSIONAL INSURANCE", "ORG"], ["400", "CARDINAL"], ["Street Alexandria", "PERSON"], ["Virginia", "GPE"], ["703", "CARDINAL"], ["703", "CARDINAL"], ["NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF \nPROFESSIONAL SURPLUS LINES OFFICES", "ORG"], ["LTD", "ORG"], ["200", "CARDINAL"], ["N.E. 54th Street", "EVENT"], ["200", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["200", "CARDINAL"], ["N.E. 54th Street", "EVENT"], ["200", "CARDINAL"], ["Kansas City", "GPE"], ["MO", "GPE"], ["64118Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["816", "CARDINAL"], ["816", "CARDINAL"], ["NATIONAL INSURANCE \nCRIME BUREAU\n", "ORG"], ["1111", "DATE"], ["Suite", "PERSON"], ["400", "CARDINAL"], ["Des Plaines", "GPE"], ["60018Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["847", "CARDINAL"], ["847", "CARDINAL"], ["NCCI HOLDINGS, INC.", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["NCCI HOLDINGS, INC.", "ORG"], ["901", "CARDINAL"], ["Peninsula Corporate", "ORG"], ["Boca Raton", "PERSON"], ["33487Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["561", "CARDINAL"], ["561", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t", "ORG"], ["NCCI, INC.", "ORG"], ["111", "CARDINAL"], ["River Street", "FAC"], ["1202", "DATE"], ["Hoboken", "GPE"], ["07030Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["201", "CARDINAL"], ["201", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["ASSOCIATION OF AMERICA", "ORG"], ["2600", "CARDINAL"], ["South River Road", "LOC"], ["Des Plaines", "GPE"], ["847", "CARDINAL"], ["847", "CARDINAL"], ["Serves", "ORG"], ["CALIFORNIA", "GPE"], ["Western Region", "LOC"], ["1415", "DATE"], ["L Street", "FAC"], ["670", "CARDINAL"], ["Sacramento", "GPE"], ["916-449-1370Fax", "CARDINAL"], ["916-449-1378Web", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["1535", "DATE"], ["Grant Street", "FAC"], ["225", "CARDINAL"], ["Denver", "GPE"], ["CO 80203Tel", "ORG"], ["303", "CARDINAL"], ["303", "CARDINAL"], ["FLORIDA", "GPE"], ["215 S. Monroe Street", "PERSON"], ["Suite", "PERSON"], ["32302Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["850-681-2615Fax", "QUANTITY"], ["850-681-2614Web", "QUANTITY"], ["GEORGIA\n6636", "ORG"], ["Church Street", "FAC"], ["Suite 300Douglasville", "GPE"], ["30134Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["770-949-1776Fax", "CARDINAL"], ["770-949-0889Web", "CARDINAL"], ["New England Region", "LOC"], ["One", "CARDINAL"], ["1500", "CARDINAL"], ["Boston", "GPE"], ["MA 02109Tel", "ORG"], ["617-723-1976Fax", "MONEY"], ["617", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["NEW JERSEY", "GPE"], ["Northeastern Region", "LOC"], ["28", "CARDINAL"], ["West State Street", "GPE"], ["Trenton", "GPE"], ["NJ 08608Tel", "ORG"], ["609", "CARDINAL"], ["609", "CARDINAL"], ["NEW YORK", "GPE"], ["90", "CARDINAL"], ["South Swan StreetAlbany", "LOC"], ["12210Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["518", "CARDINAL"], ["518", "CARDINAL"], ["116", "CARDINAL"], ["Harrisburg", "GPE"], ["17101Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["717", "CARDINAL"], ["717", "CARDINAL"], ["TEXAS", "GPE"], ["Southwestern Region", "LOC"], ["Lavaca Street", "FAC"], ["1400", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["Lavaca Street", "FAC"], ["Suite", "PERSON"], ["Austin", "PERSON"], ["512", "CARDINAL"], ["847", "CARDINAL"], ["WASHINGTON", "GPE"], ["Northwestern Region", "LOC"], ["1500", "CARDINAL"], ["2", "CARDINAL"], ["98501Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["360-915-6268Fax: 360-357-5343Web", "QUANTITY"], ["132", "CARDINAL"], ["WASHINGTON", "GPE"], ["DC", "GPE"], ["444", "CARDINAL"], ["North Capitol Street NW", "ORG"], ["801", "CARDINAL"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["20001Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["1301", "DATE"], ["Pennsylvania Avenue", "FAC"], ["Suite", "PERSON"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["DC", "GPE"], ["20004Tel", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["SURETY & FIDELITY ASSOCIATION \nOF AMERICA", "ORG"], ["1101", "DATE"], ["Connecticut Avenue", "FAC"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["SURETY INFORMATION OFFICE\n", "ORG"], ["1828", "DATE"], ["L Street", "EVENT"], ["720", "CARDINAL"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["Life/Health \nInsurance Industry Organizations \nAMERICA", "ORG"], ["AHIP", "ORG"], ["601", "CARDINAL"], ["Pennsylvania Avenue NW", "FAC"], ["South", "LOC"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["601", "CARDINAL"], ["Pennsylvania Avenue NW", "FAC"], ["South \nBuilding", "GPE"], ["Suite 500Washington, DC 20004  Tel", "GPE"], ["202-778", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["www.ahip.orgNational trade association representing health insurance", "ORG"], ["AMERICAN COUNCIL OF \nLIFE INSURERS (ACLI", "ORG"], ["101 Constitution Avenue NW", "MONEY"], ["700", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["101 Constitution Avenue NW", "MONEY"], ["700", "CARDINAL"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["20001-2133", "DATE"], ["Tel", "PERSON"], ["202-624", "CARDINAL"], ["202-572", "CARDINAL"], ["THE LIFE AND HEALTH INSURANCE \nFOUNDATION FOR", "ORG"], ["1655", "DATE"], ["North Fort Myer Drive", "FAC"], ["610", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["1655", "DATE"], ["North Fort Myer Drive", "FAC"], ["Suite", "PERSON"], ["610", "CARDINAL"], ["Arlington", "GPE"], ["888", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t", "ORG"], ["133Directories", "CARDINAL"], ["1011", "DATE"], ["East Colonial Drive", "FAC"], ["500", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["1011", "DATE"], ["East Colonial Drive", "FAC"], ["500", "CARDINAL"], ["Orlando", "GPE"], ["407-894-3797Fax", "QUANTITY"], ["407", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["LIMRA INTERNATIONAL\n", "ORG"], ["Hill RoadWindsor", "ORG"], ["CT", "ORG"], ["860", "CARDINAL"], ["860", "CARDINAL"], ["more than 60", "CARDINAL"], ["Windy Ridge Parkway", "FAC"], ["600", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["2300", "DATE"], ["Windy Ridge Parkway", "FAC"], ["600", "CARDINAL"], ["Atlanta", "GPE"], ["30339-8443", "DATE"], ["770-951-1770Fax", "CARDINAL"], ["770-984-0441Web", "QUANTITY"], ["MIB", "ORG"], ["50", "CARDINAL"], ["Braintree Hill Park", "LOC"], ["MA 02184-8734", "ORG"], ["781", "CARDINAL"], ["1995.NATIONAL", "CARDINAL"], ["ALLIANCE OF \nLIFE COMPANIES", "ORG"], ["NALC", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["NALC", "ORG"], ["Sarasota", "GPE"], ["941-379", "CARDINAL"], ["941-379", "CARDINAL"], ["NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF \nHEALTH UNDERWRITERS", "ORG"], ["2000", "DATE"], ["North 14th Street", "EVENT"], ["450", "CARDINAL"], ["Arlington", "GPE"], ["VA", "GPE"], ["Tel", "PERSON"], ["703", "CARDINAL"], ["703-841-7797Web", "QUANTITY"], ["NATIONAL ORGANIZATION \nOF LIFE AND HEALTH INSURANCE GUARANTY ASSOCIATIONS", "ORG"], ["NOLHGA", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["13873", "DATE"], ["Park Center Road", "FAC"], ["329", "CARDINAL"], ["Herndon", "GPE"], ["VA", "GPE"], ["703", "CARDINAL"], ["703", "CARDINAL"], ["50", "CARDINAL"], ["the District of Columbia", "GPE"], ["Puerto Rico", "GPE"], ["NOLHGA", "ORG"], ["134", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["Financial \nServices Industry Organizations \nADVANTAGE GROUP \nASSOCIATES, INC.\n", "ORG"], ["215", "CARDINAL"], ["IA", "GPE"], ["Tel", "PERSON"], ["515-262-2623Web", "CARDINAL"], ["third", "ORDINAL"], ["AMERICAN BANKERS ASSOCIATION", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["AMERICAN BANKERS ASSOCIATION\n", "ORG"], ["1120", "DATE"], ["Connecticut Avenue NWWashington", "FAC"], ["202", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["AMERICAN BANKERS \nINSURANCE ASSOCIATION\n", "ORG"], ["1120", "DATE"], ["Connecticut Avenue", "FAC"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["202-663-5163Fax", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["the American Bankers Association", "ORG"], ["AMERICAN FINANCIAL \nSERVICES ASSOCIATION", "ORG"], ["115", "CARDINAL"], ["LaSalle Street", "FAC"], ["3300", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["115", "CARDINAL"], ["S. LaSalle Street", "ORG"], ["3300", "CARDINAL"], ["Chicago", "GPE"], ["IL 60603-3801  Tel", "ORG"], ["800-224", "CARDINAL"], ["312", "CARDINAL"], ["BANK ADMINISTRATION INSTITUTE", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["BANK ADMINISTRATION INSTITUTE", "ORG"], ["One", "CARDINAL"], ["IL 60606-3421 Tel", "ORG"], ["888", "CARDINAL"], ["800-375", "CARDINAL"], ["Basel", "GPE"], ["Centralbahnplatz 2", "PERSON"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["Basel", "GPE"], ["Centralbahnplatz 2\nBasel", "PERSON"], ["Switzerland", "GPE"], ["41-61", "CARDINAL"], ["41-61", "CARDINAL"], ["I.I.I.\tInsurance\tHandbook\t\t\twww.iii.org/insurancehandbook\t \t135Directories\nBANK INSURANCE & \nSECURITIES ASSOCIATION\n", "ORG"], ["303", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["303", "CARDINAL"], ["Suite 2D\nWayne", "ORG"], ["610", "CARDINAL"], ["610", "CARDINAL"], ["154", "CARDINAL"], ["East Boston Post Road", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["RESEARCH GROUP", "ORG"], ["154", "CARDINAL"], ["East Boston Post Road\nMamaroneck", "ORG"], ["10543", "DATE"], ["914-381", "CARDINAL"], ["823", "CARDINAL"], ["King of Prussia Road", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["823", "CARDINAL"], ["King of Prussia Road\nRadnor", "ORG"], ["PA 19087", "DATE"], ["Tel", "PERSON"], ["610", "CARDINAL"], ["610", "CARDINAL"], ["monthly", "DATE"], ["1425", "DATE"], ["K Street NW", "ORG"], ["500", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["1425", "DATE"], ["K Street NW", "ORG"], ["500", "CARDINAL"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["NETWORK", "ORG"], ["PO Box", "ORG"], ["11910", "DATE"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["NETWORK", "ORG"], ["PO Box", "ORG"], ["11910", "DATE"], ["Lexington", "GPE"], ["40578-1910", "DATE"], ["859-244-8175Web", "QUANTITY"], ["the National Association of State Treasurers", "ORG"], ["Network", "ORG"], ["THE COMMITTEE OF \nANNUITY", "ORG"], ["Davis & Harman LLP", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["ANNUITY", "ORG"], ["Davis & Harman LLP\n", "ORG"], ["1455", "DATE"], ["Pennsylvania Avenue NW", "EVENT"], ["1200", "CARDINAL"], ["202-347", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["136", "CARDINAL"], ["Three Lafayette Centre", "ORG"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["1155", "DATE"], ["21st Street NWWashington", "FAC"], ["DC", "GPE"], ["202-418", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"], ["Congress", "ORG"], ["1155", "DATE"], ["Connecticut Avenue NW", "EVENT"], ["5th Floor", "ORG"], ["Washington", "GPE"], ["202-296", "CARDINAL"], ["202", "CARDINAL"]], "topic": 0}, {"entities": [["Wilson Boulevard", "ORG"], ["2500", "CARDINAL"], ["Arlington", "GPE"], ["703", "CARDINAL"], ["703", "CARDINAL"], ["DMA FINANCIAL SERVICES COUNCIL", "O